Guide to the Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
- Series II. Assignments
  - Luncheon at ILR with Lin Paltrow speaking., Apr. 7, 1987; 1294; 19 (Box 24)
  - Symposium for Urie Bronfenbrenner to Emeritus Professor., Apr. 26, 1987; 1295; 226 (Box 24)
  - Helen Vandervort- HE alumni and member of advisory council touring the new Savage Hall addition with Dean Zeigler, Apr. 24, 1987; 1296; 10 (Box 24)
  - HE Activities: Sheet#1: Gertrude Armbruster/Nut. Sci. with students doing microwave oven research., Apr. 27, 1987; 1297; 37 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#2: Pat Bauman- HE Senior with school children at Central School working on Nutrition Education Program, Apr. 28, 1987; 1297; 17 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#3,4,5: Senior Alumni Reception at Johnson Art Museum, Apr. 15, 1988; 1297; 94 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#6&7: HE Graduation room beginning to end, (when they were lining up right on through into stands). Then reception in MVR., May 29, 1988; 1297; 73 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#8,9,10,11: Dean Zeigler's retirement party - "Jerry's Jubilee" held in MVR with skits and speakers and barbecue on Ag. Quad in tent., June 14, 1988; 1297; 132 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#12: Gret Atkins and Anita Stuever looking at publications in Ellen Bonn's office. To be used for TXA exhibit., Nov. 17, 1988; 1297; 37 (Box 24)
  - Hatch Centennial Symposium, May 4&5, 1987; 1298; 256 (Box 24)
  - Computer game (unique course in Health Administration) with students and Doug Brown., May 7, 1987; 1299; 41 (Box 24)
  - Students, professors, in lab and classrooms - both long and short shots, some demonstrations., May 8, 1987; 1300; 64 (Box 24)
  - People riding tractors and planting at Farm Services area near Bluegrass Lane for John Whitcomb's class in Comm., May 6, 1987; 1301; 31 (Box 24)
  - Nutrition Faculty. Sheet#1: Frames 7-17-Asst. Prof. Nut. Sci. Kathy Rasmussen. Frames 16-24 Michael N. Kazarinoff-Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci., May 7, 1987; 1302; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#2: Frames 25-27:Michael N. Kazarinoff-Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci.. Frames 29-38: Ruth Schwartz- Prof. Nut. Sci., May 7, 1987; 1302; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#3: Frames 1-5: Ruth Schwartz- Prof. Nut. Sci.; Frames 6-12: Jean Apagar-Research Chem./USDA Agr. Res. Serv., May 7, 1987; 1302; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#4: Frames 4-12: Ardyth Gillespie-Asso.Prof. Nut. Sci., May 7, 1987; 1302; 6 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#5: Frames 13-27. Andre Bensadoun-Prof. Nut. Biochem., May 7, 1987; 1302; 10 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#6: Frames 2-20. Nell Mondy- Prof. Food Sci and Toxic/Nut. Sci, May 7, 1987; 1302; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#7: Frames 29-38: Nell Mondy- Prof. Food Sci and Toxic/Nut. Sci, May 7, 1987; 1302; 7 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#8: Frames 21-38. Lani Stephenson- Asst. Prof. Nut. Sci., May 7, 1987; 1302; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#9: Frames 2-5: Lani Stephenson- Asst. Prof. Nut. Sci.; Frames 7-20: Chris Olson-Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci., May 7, 1987; 1302; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#10: Frames 21-23 Chris Olson-Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci./ Frames 25-38: Nancy Peckenpaugh-Lec.Nut.Sci., May 8, 1987; 1302; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #11: Frames 2-5 Peter Van Soest - Prof. Ani. Sci. & Nut./ Frames 17-20: Marcia Pimental- Senior Lect. Nut. Sci., May 8, 1987; 1302; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#12: Frames 20-30: Marcia Pimental- Senior Lect. Nut. Sci./ Frames 31-37: Richard Warner- professor Ani. Sci., May 8, 1987; 1302; 11 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#13: Frames 3-13: Paddy Redihan - Ext. Asso./Nut. Sci./Frames 14-21: Margaret Day-Extension Asso., May 12, 1987; 1302; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#14: Frame 22: Margaret Day-Extension Asso./ Frames 24-37: Jere D. Haas- Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci., May 12, 1987; 1302; 11 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#15: Frames 1-15: Pat Thonney - Ext. Asso. /Nut. Sci.; Frames 16-18: Bertha G. Lewis (Betty)- Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci., May 13, 1987; 1302; 11 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #16: Frames 3-6: Bertha G. Lewis (Betty)- Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci.; Frames 7-13: Michael C. Latham- Prof. International Nutrition & Director of Program for International Nutrition.; Frames 15-17: Mary Morrison- Professor Nut. Sciences., May 13, 1987; 1302; 10 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#17: Frames 2-9 Mary Morrison- Professor Nut. Sciences./ Frames 10-18: Diva Sanjur- Prof Life Sciences, May 13, 1987; 1302; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#18: Frames 3-8: Murial Brink- Prof. Nut. Sciences; Frames 7-16: Joannie Siegler- Lect. Nut. Sci.; Frames 17-20: Darrell Van Campen - Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci. & Lab. Dir. USDA Agr. Res. Service, May 13, 1987; 1302; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#19: Frames 22-32: Darrell Van Campen - Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci. & Lab. Dir. USDA Agr. Res. Service; Frames 34-37: Rosemary Holmes: Lecturer Nut. Sci., May 14, 1987; 1302; 11 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#20: Frames 3-8: Rosemary Holmes: Lecturer Nut. Sci. / Frames 9-18: Barbara Strupp- Research Asso. III/Nut. Sci., May 14, 1987; 1302; 11 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#21: Frames 3-15: Tracy Farrell- Extension Asso. II/ Nut. Sci, May 15, 1987; 1302; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #22: Frames 1-9: Mary Fran Sowers- Asst. Prol. Nut. Sci, May 15, 1987; 1302; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#23: Frames 2-19: Nell Mondy- Prof Food Sci& Toxic/ Nut. Sci., June 5, 1987; 1302; 10 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#24: Frames 1-19: Richard Austic- Asso. Prof. Animal Nutrition & Poultry Avian Sciences, June 5, 1987; 1302; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#25: Frames 2-13: Barb Clary/ Extension Associate, June 3, 1987; 1302; 8 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#26: Frames 19-36: Ardyth Gillespie- Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci., June 17, 1987; 1302; 10 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#27: Frames 2-9: Cathy C. Campbell: Asst. Prof. Nut. Sci., July 28, 1987; 1302; 6 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#27: Frames 11-19: Betty Lewis - Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci., July 28, 1987; 1302; 6 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#28: Frames 1-11: Betty Lewis - Asso. Prof. Nut. Sci., July 28, 1987; 1302; 7 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#29: Frames 1-12: Donna Evans- Lecturer Nut. Sci., Aug. 5, 1987; 1302; 8 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#30: Frames 29-30A: Cuthburto Garza/ New Director DNS, May 25, 1988; 1302; 5 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#31: Frames 15-18: Charles McCormick/ Asst. Prof DNS, Jan. 10, 1988; 1302; 3 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#32: Frames 2-10: David Pelletier- Research Asso. DNS., Oct. 25, 1988; 1302; 6 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#32: Frames 13-21: Elizabeth Wien- Research Asso/ DNS, Oct. 25, 1988; 1302; 6 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #33: Frames 22-31: Roger Shrimpton- Res. Asso./ DNS., Oct. 25, 1988; 1302; 6 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #33: Frames 27:35: David Quig- Res. Asso. DNS, Oct. 26, 1988; 1302; 6 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#34: Frames 3-9: Frances Thompson- Res. Asso. DNS, Oct. 26, 1988; 1302; 5 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#35: Frames 6-16: Diva Sanjur- Prof. Nut. Sci., Dec. 7, 1988; 1302; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#36: Frames 4-22: DNS Advisory Committee Meeting, Jan. 31, 1989; 1302; 19 (Box 24)
  - Sheet# 36: Frames 23-26: David Sahn- Member of CFNPP, Jan. 31, 1989; 1302; 4 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#36: Frames 27-31: Carlo del Nino- Member of CFNPP, Jan. 31, 1989; 1302; 4 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#36: Frames 32-34: Fred Roche- Member of CFNPP (Cornell Food & Nutrition Policy Program), Jan. 31, 1989; 1302; 3 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#37: Anne Kendall Casella- Research Associate, DNS, July 31, 1989; 1302; 7 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#38: Pat Casano- Research Associate, DNS, Aug. 1, 1989; 1302; 6 (Box 24)
  - Senior BBQ in Judging Pavilion, May 29, 1987; 1303; 65 (Box 24)
  - Animal Science Faculty: Sheet#1: Frames 26-32: Charles J. Sniffen/ Prof. Ani. Sci.; Frames 33-36a: Alan. W. Bell/ Asst. Prof. Ani. Sci., May 18, 1987; 1304; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#2: Frames 1-6: Danny G. Fox/ Asso. Prof. Ani. Sci; Frames 7-12: Walter Ronald Butler/ Asso. Prof. Ani. Sci.; Frames 13-23: Bruce W, Currie/ Asso .Prof. Ani. Sci; Frames 31-36a: Robert H. Foote/ Prof. Ani. Sci., May 18, 1987; 1304; 36 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#3: Frames 1-3: Robert H. Foote/ Prof. Ani. Sci.; Frames 4-10: Harold F. Hintz/ Prof. Ani. Sci; Frames 11-21: Professor Douglas E. Houge/ Pro. Ani. Sci.; Frames 14-1: Terry R. Smith/ Asst. Prof. Ani. Sci., May 18, 1987; 1304; 36 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#4: Frames 1-6: Larry Chase/ Assoc. Prof. Ani. Sci:; Frames 7-13: Samuel W. Sabin/ Prof. Ani. Sci; Frames20-29: Ronald. C. Gorewit/ Asso. Prof. Ani. Sci; Frames 30-34: Donald E. Beermann/ Asso. Prof. Ani. Sci.; Frames 14-19: Terry R. Smith/ Asst. Prof. Ani. Sci, May 19, 1987; 1304; 34 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#5: Frames 1-6a: Pascal A. Oltenacu/ Assoc. Prof. Ani. Sci; Frames 7-11: James R. Stouffer/ Prof. Ani. Sci.; Frames 12-18a: Richard L. Quass/ Asso. Prof. Ani. Sci; Frames 19-23: James B. Russell/ Asso. Prof. Ani. Sci; Frames 24-30a: Michael L. Thonney/ Asoc. Prof. Ani. Sci.; Frames 31-36a: Tro V. Bui/ Ext. Assoc. Ani. Sci, May 20, 1987; 1304; 36 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#6: Frames 0-9a: Robert W. Everett: Prof. Ani. Sci; Frames 10-15a: Wm. G. Merrill/ Prof. Ani. Sci; Frames 16-36a: Tro. V. Bui/ Ext. Asso. Ani. Sci, May 20, 1987; 1304; 26 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #7: Frames 2-10 Wm. Green/ Ext. Asso. Ani. Sci, June 11, 1987; 1304; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#8: Frames 1-3 Corwin Holtz/ Instructor of 4-H Dairy and Small Pets Prog., June 3, 1987; 1304; 5 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#8: Frames 6-18: Mary Jean Wylie/ Asoc. Prof. Ani. Sci., June 3, 1987; 1304; 7 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#9: Frames 7-15: Robert Blake / Assoc. Prof. Ani. Sci, Aug. 29, 1988; 1304; 6 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#9: Frames 10-16: Dean Boyd: Asso. Prof. Ani. Sci, Aug. 29, 1988; 1304; 5 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#10: John Parks/ Asst. Prof. Ani. Sci., Aug. 19, 1988; 1304; 6 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#11: David DeVol- Assistant Prof. Ani. Sci., Feb. 15, 1989; 1304; 7 (Box 24)
  - Graduation and Ag. College Reception, May 1987; 1305; 76 (Box 24)
  - Photos taken for publication "Getting to Know Your Child's School". Sheet #1&2: Northeast Elem School principal Michael Ouckama in his office on the telephone., June 8, 1987; 1306; 20 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#3: Barbara Eshelman/ Senior Extension Associate, June 8, 1987; 1306; 10 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #4&5: Teacher Denise Lee in her classroom at Central School with students., June 12, 1987; 1306; 46 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #6&7: Steve Hamilton with his son reading in their home., Aug. 12, 1987; 1306; 16 (Box 24)
  - ALS News, Sheet #1&2: ALS breakfast., June 13, 1987; 1307; 48 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #3: ALS reunion booth, June 12, 1987; 1307; 11 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #4: Harvesting Brook Trout at Hartford, NY., June 15, 1987; 1307; 23 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#5: Arnot Forest 4-H teens using video equipment for environmental educator., June 24, 1987; 1307; 30 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#6: Deborah Streeter- Asst. Prof. In Ag. Econ in her office and at blackboard., July 22, 1987; 1307; 15 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#7: Dave Van Metre- Vet College student giving calf a physical exam in the Large Animal Clinic., July 21, 1987; 1307; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#8: Daniel Aneshansley with a vacuum he developed to clean potato plants of bugs in a potato field., July 24, 1987; 1307; 20 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#9: Peter Steponkus- Prof. Agronomy in his office in Bradfield Hall, Aug. 4, 1987; 1307; 11 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#10: Vegetables being plucked and displayed in the Plantations-Pounder Heritage Gardens, Sept. 9, 1987; 1307; 30 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#11: Deflectometer - checks road surface conditions with Cheryl Richter, Charles Ditmars in the "k" lot., Sept. 16, 1987; 1307; 25 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#12: Jan Olsen/Director of Mann and Edward McLaughlin Asst. Prof Ag. Econ. Olsen teaching McLaughlin to use compact disk information retrieval system., Sept. 25, 1987; 1307; 7 (Box 24)
  - Sheet# 13: Laeo Carter portrait, Oct. 9, 1987; 1307; 10 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#14: Yves Boisclair- Grad student in Animal Sci, recipient of award from Purina Mills, Feb. 17, 1988; 1307; 8 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#15: Two seniors in Communication Denise Filler and Margaret McHugh with Becky Bilderback, the Director of Better Housing in Tompkins County., Feb. 19, 1988; 1307; 30 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#16: Ed Jones: Prof. Plant Path in his office., Mar. 21, 1988; 1307; 7 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#17: Ellis Loew: Assoc. Prof Vet Physiology, .; 1307 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#18: Ed Jones in greenhouse at the Uihlein Farm in Lake Placid, NY - shots of potato seed propagation., Mar. 24,25, 1988; 1307; 13 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#19: Frames 11, 12 (B & W), Frames 11, 12, 14, painting of Henry Uihlein II, Frames 15,17,18: Ed Jones and his wife witting in front of a painting/ portrait of Henry Uihlein., Mar. 24,25, 1988; 1307; 6color, 2B & W (Box 24)
  - Sheet#20: Tim Fahey- Nat. Resources- examining a tree root with a hand lens (looking at changes in tree roots in the forest)., May 26, 1988; 1307; 11 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#21: Growth Hormones ratio fat to lean in swine being checked by Donald Beermann/ Animal Swine, May 25, 1988; 1307; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #22, 23, 24: ALS Breakfast 1988, June 11, 1988; 1307; 84 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #25: Ben Bradley at the reception at the Big Red Barn for the Conn. Hill Student Internship Fund., June 8, 1988; 1307; 7 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#26: Paul Tilly- Incoming President of CALS Alumni Asso., June 2, 1988; 1307; 7 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#27: Alumni reunion candids at Camp Arnot- Arnot Forest., June 9, 1988; 1307; 15 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#28: Group photo of approx. 20 alumns at Camp Arnot., June 9, 1988; 1307; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#29: Molly Kyle- (PHD from Cornell) Post Doc in Genetics with her assistant Malka Korman recent grad from Cornell in Bradfield Hall lab., June 22, 1988; 1307; 7 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #30: David Winkler's bird class with students handling birds, also bird collection shots., Oct. 4, 1988; 1307; 24 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#31: Amy McClune's class handling fish also fish collection, Oct. 3, 1988; 1307; 36 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#32: Portrait of Donna Teebagy/ Ag. Communications Major 1989., Feb. 24, 1989; 1307; 10 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#33: Ag in the classroom/ lambs and students in classroom at the Dryden Elementary School., Mar. 16, 1989; 1307; 13 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #34: Frames 2a-7a: Edgar Raffensperger and Gerri Gay sitting near computer. Frames 8a-14-computer screen with various images., Mar. 27, 1989; 1307; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheets 35 & 36: Computer screen with various images and on sheet 36 photos of disk by itself., Mar. 27, 1989; 1307; 17 (Box 24)
  - HE News: Sheet#1: Frames 1, 2, 3: HE Breakfast ( see enclosed notes); on sheet 3 - frames 3, 4, 5: - Lawrence Loo - 1987 HE grad., June 12, 1987; 1308; 82 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#4: Class of 1919 Alum- Edith Bickford with her grandchildren - the grandchildren have set up a scholarship fund in HE. Mark Schofield, Paul Schofield, Ann Rice., June 26, 1987; 1308; 25 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#5: HE student profile/ Ress Bradford in Nut. Lab., July 28, 1987; 1308; 7 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#6: Luncheon reception for Jan Crance., Dec. 4, 1987; 1308; 25 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#7: Frames 1-3: Sarah Ann Sembach, Evelyn Stout, Mary Purchase, Vasudha Ravichandrau- candidate TXA; Frames 4-6: Sarah Ann Sembach, Evelyn Stout; Frames 7-10: Mary Purchase, Vasudha Ravichandrau; Frames 22-25: Albert Nolin, Engr'21 and Anita Shrods '91. Frames 26-27: Helen Vandevort, '26, Al Nolin, '21 Engr.; Frames 28-29: Helen Vandevort, Al Nolin, Carolyn Cook; Frames 30-31: Al Nolin, Carolyn Cook; Frames 32-35: Betty Lee 1989, Dec. 7, 1987; 1308; 24 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#8: Frames 1-5 & 36a: Susan Payne/ Admin Aide Alumni Office, HE.; Frames 6-11: Pat Reed/ Assistant Director, Alumni Office, HE.; Frames 32-36: Horace Shackelton, Sr-ALS'19 and Stacey Sueishi 1988., Dec. 7, 1987; 1308; 17 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#9: Informal student profile of HE Senior Rob Grossman in his frat house living room (Theta Chi Frat)., Feb. 8, 1988; 1308; 5 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#10: HE Alumni & Residence Program breakfast with Jim Hazard/Susan Dey and Faculty in Residence, Faculty Fellows and Alumni in Residence., Mar. 7, 1988; 1308; 11 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#11: Cewin Chao/HE student portait., Mar. 14, 1988; 1308; 11 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#12: Pamela Meyers- visiting lecturer in DEA., Mar. 14, 1988; 1308; 13 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#13: John Alexander- President of CBORD, a software firm- lecturing in Mann Lib. He is the Dorothy Proud lecturer for this year., Mar. 4, 1988; 1308; 31 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#14: Symposium on membership with Steve Hamilton/Chairman., Mar. 28, 1988; 1308; 30 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#15&16: Exhibition and reception at Johnson Art Museum of Jon Haggins- minority designer from NYC., Apr. 9, 1988; 1308; 30 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#17: Stephanie Swan- HE undergrad on bridge overlooking Beebe Lake Falls. She is the recipient of the student research award from the American Federation for Clinical Research., May 2, 1988; 1308; 4 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#18&19: Reception for Nancy Saltford leaving as Asso. Dean of Human Ecology. The reception was held in the A.D.White House., May 26, 1988; 1308; 44 (Box 24)
  - Sheet 20, 21, 22: HE Breakfast, June 10, 1988; 1308; 82 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #23 &24: Savage Hall wing. (Dean Zeigler, C. Cook, M. Neshein), also photos of the entrance to the old section and the new wing of Savage Hall which connects the two buildings., June 10, 1988; 1308; 30 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #23 &24: Savage Hall wing. (Dean Zeigler, C. Cook, M. Neshein), also photos of the entrance to the old section and the new wing of Savage Hall which connects the two buildings., June 10, 1988; 1308; 5 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#25: Portrait of incoming Dean of Human Ecology - Dean Francille Firebaugh taken in Deans' office MVR., Aug. 6, 1988; 1308; 10 (Box 24)
  - Sheet #26 & 27: Carolyn Cook's farewell party in MRV Faculty Lounge., Aug. 11, 1988; 1308; 48 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#28: a 15' modern steel structure on lawn in front of Johnson Museum named "Remembrance" created by Vermont sculptor David Brender, '55 graduate of Ag & Life Sciences., Sept. 1988; 1308; 16 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#29: Peter Dedek, HE DEA student illustrating Prof. Beckman's teaching on computer., Aug. 31, 1988; 1308; 13 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#30: Alum-Nancy Clark putting up her display in the exhibit case on the bridge between old and new MVR., Sept. 9, 1988; 1308; 15 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#31: Alumnus of HE- Nancy Harrington lecturing in Susan Hester's TXA class., Sept. 29, 1988; 1308; 36 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#32: Frames 1-14: Guest lecturer Kitty Daly (HE Alum from late 60's) talking with TXA students., Oct. 11, 1988; 1308; 14 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#32: Frames 15-24: Bruce Laingen (former Iranian hostage) talking with TXA students., Oct. 11, 1988; 1308; 10 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#33: Carol Aslanean- HE Alum mixing with others in MVR Faculty Commons., Oct. 14, 1988; 1308; 17 (Box 24)
  - Sheet# 34: NFL Workshop Frames 1-5: NYC group at table. Frames 6-9: Dr. Neshiem at podium; Frames 10-23: Matilda Cuomo at podium; Frames 24-26: both Dr. Nesheim and M. Cuomo at podium. Frames 27-31: NFL Team group photo. All this was taken at Sheraton Inn for the NFL conference., Nov. 14, 1988; 1308; 31 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#35: Frames 0-7: Reiko Mazuka- HDFS Grad Student., Dec. 9, 1988; 1308; 8 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#35: Frames 8-36a: Susan Hester at game board with students., Dec. 9, 1988; 1308; 30 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#36: Mary Anne Schuler- new Director of HE Alumni Aff. And Development., Jan. 17, 1989; 1308; 12 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#37: Frames 1-5: Halpern Prize Award Ceremony with Kristina Schneider and Dean Firebaugh., Jan. 27, 1989; 1308; 5 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#38: Dean Francine Firebaugh- informal shots before lecture with others and at the podium., Jan. 30, 1989; 1308; 28 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#39: Photo taken of Michael Saunders running in Barton Hall to be used for student profile., Feb. 6, 1989; 1308; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#40: HE Alum Susan Ligouri speaking with students in HE/MVR Faculty Lounge., Feb. 14, 1989; 1308; 32 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#41: CEH Mojor- Dean's Scholar James Mister portrait., Mar. 6, 1989; 1308; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#42: HE undergrad Outstanding Student Michelle Marshall, Mar. 13, 1989; 1308; 10 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#43: HE student advisors (fake session) Susan Freund, Debra Wein, Patti Levine., Mar. 16, 1989; 1308; 18 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#44: HE admissions staff looking through folders in admissions office., Mar. 28, 1989; 1308; 27 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#45: HE Minority student Elizabeth O'Neil sitting at table., Mar. 29, 1989; 1308; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#46&47: Alumni panel discussion on careers in MRV Faculty Lounge., Apr. 13, 1989; 1308; 41 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#48&49: HE reception for Dean's List students/Presentation to the two top students in each class., Apr. 17, 1989; 1308; 48 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#50: Student presentation/Apparel Design by HE students ( modeling and candids), May 8, 1989; 1308; 20 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#51: Dean Firebaugh and Alice McCarthy (Alumni and member of HE Advisor Council). Alice received the Dean's Award for Public Service., May 5, 1989; 1308; 16 (Box 24)
  - Lou Minns Gardens, June 1987; 1309; 10 (Box 24)
  - Empire Farm Days, Sheet #1,2,3: Holstein steers in barn at T & R CTR. Sheets#4,5,6: Bill Harrower and Phil Day-Energy Audit Specialists for Coop. Ext. at Harford T & R CTR. Sheet#7: Dave Hill - Energy Audit Specialist in Steuben County- Bath, NY., June 30, 1987; 1310; 63 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#8: Dave Hill - Energy Audit Specialist in Steuben County- Bath, NY., June 30, 1987; 1310; 12 color (Box 24)
  - Sheet#9: Bill Harrower and Phil Day-Energy Audit Specialists for Coop. Ext. at Harford T & R CTR., June 30, 1987; 1310; 12 color (Box 24)
  - Sheets#10,11,12,13: Exterior scenes at Harford T & R CTR., July 14, 1987; 1310; 36 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#14: Snap beans at Veg. Crops Test Garden, July 1987; 1310; 9 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#15: General T & R farm scenes (exterior)., July 1987; 1310; 34 (Box 24)
  - Nancy Meltzer's retirement party in MVR/Faculty Commons, June 26, 1987; 1311; 43 (Box 24)
  - Photos taken for Nutrition For Life Poster. Sheet#1: Children eating. Sheet#2: People in MVR cafeteria and people shopping. Sheet#3: People walking in the neighborhood of W. Buffalo St. Sheet#4: Children eating and people walking in W. Buffalo St.area., July 21, 1987; 1312; 126 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#5: Nutrition for Life logo, July 1988; 1312; 24 (Box 24)
  - Humphrey Fellows/ photos to be used in Humphrey brochure. Sheet#1: Frames 1-5: Ramesh Singh Pradhan. Frames 6-10: Mamadoll Camara. Frames 12-16: Kebede Tesfaye. Frames 17-21: Elizabeth Madraa. Frames 22-26: Panpilai Kitsudsaeng. Frames 29-33: Kemal Taruc., July 16, 1987; 1313; 30 (Box 24)
  - Sheet#2: Frames 1-5: Edgar Guardia, Frames 6-10: John Mudusa. Frames 11-17a: Kamas A Kamaruddin, Frames 18-21: Robindra Adhikary, Frames 22-25: William Amezquita-Andrada, Aug. 25, 1987; 1313; 25 (Box 24)
  - Food Executive Program, July 1987; 1314; 336 (Box 24)
  - Chain Drugstore group photos/candids and picnic, etc., July 1987; 1315; 96 (Box 24)
  - Cornell Biological Field Station at Shakelton Point, NY., July 30,31, 1987; 1316; 259 (Box 24)
  - Keys to Rural Development group shot. (Foreign students plus three faculty members in Int. Ag.), Aug. 17, 1987; 1317; 5 (Box 24)
  - Soil Taxonomy frames shot from video tape in Radio Center, Aug. 21, 1987; 1318; 64 (Box 24)
  - Cornell Soccer Camp kids playing soccer on Schoellkoph Field wearing TXA athletic apparel., Aug. 18, 1987; 1319; 28 (Box 24)
  - Corn fields- taken with Bill Cox: Agronomy for publication., Aug. 20, 1987; 1320; 36 (Box 25)
  - Pomology Staff: Sheet#1:Frames 1-11: David Blanpied/Professor. Frames 12-20" Lee Creasy/Professor., Aug. 24, 1987; 1321; 12 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#2: Frames 21-30: Gene Oberly/ Chairman & Prof. Pom. / Frames 31-38: Frank Liu/Professor., Aug. 24, 1987; 1321; 12 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#3: Frames 28-37: Gene Oberly/ Chair and Prof. Pom., Sept. 14, 1987; 1321; 6 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#4: Frames 1-17: Warren Stiles/Prof. Pomology. Frames 18-20: Marvin Pritts: Assistant Prof., Sept. 9, 1987; 1321; 12 (Box 25)
  - Sheet#5: Frames 21-32: Marvin Pritts/Assistant prof, Sept. 9, 1987; 1321; 8 (Box 25)
  - State Fair 1987: Sheet#1: Governor's Day/general candids (Sheet 1A), Aug. 31, 1987; 1322; 29cn (Box 25)
  - Sheet#2: Ag & Health/candids, Aug. 31, 1987; 1322; 26cn (Box 25)
  - Sheet#3: 4-H Candids, Aug. 31, 1987; 1322; 21 cn (Box 25)
  - Sheet#4: Governor's Day candids, Aug. 31, 1987; 1322; 26 cn (Box 25)